Hamse Hassan Abdillahi

CONTACT ME



Addres 150, G/libax district, Hargeysa



Phone 63-4795182



hamzehazzan21@gmail.com

PRO SKILLS

DATABASE DESIGN AND ADMINISTRATION

REACT.JS

NODE.JS

EXPRESS.JS

MANGODB

FOLLOW ME

Facebook facebook.com/hamse zancaani

linkedin linkedin.com/in/hamse zancaani

Twitter twitter.com/hamse zancaani

I am MERN stack developer. I am passionate about building web applications and have experience using technologies such as MongoDB, Express, React,NextJs,TypeScript and Node.js.I have completed several projects using the MERN stack, which have helped me develop my skills in full-stack development, database management, and server-side programming.In addition to my technical skills, I am a quick learner and enjoy working collaboratively with other developers to solve complex problems.



EXPERIENCE

2022 - 2023

self Freelancer

FREELANCE DATABASE ADMINISTRATOR

- *Tasks and overall duties: Designed, implemented, and managed a variety of database systems
- Optimized database performance
 Backed up and restored databases
 Migrated data between databases
- *Resolved database errors and problems Provided database support to users

2021 - 2023

Al Hikma Designs

GRAPHIC DESIGNER AND MOTION GRAPHICS

Tasks and overall duties:

- •Developed creative design for print materials, brochures, banners, and signs.
- •Met with customers to present mockups and collect information for adjustments.
- •Developed motion graphics for social media campaigns and website animations.
- •Managed social media accounts for clients, developing and executing content strategies.



EDUCATION

2019 - 2022

Admas University

BACHELORS OF SCIENCE IN INFORMATION COMMUNCATION TECHNOLOGY

Graduated with 14 batch ICT class of 2022 with 3.91 out 4.00 Cumulative GPA and awarded Very Great Distinacion Merit Award

2014 - 2018 Salaama Secondary School



Projects

DENTAL MANAGEMNT SYSTEM

is a software application that helps dental practices manage their patient records, appointments, treatment plans, billing, and other administrative tasks.

DMS systems can be cloud-based or on-premises, and they can be used by practices of all sizes.

• JOB FINDER WEB APP

is a Job Finder Web App is an online platform designed to help individuals in their search for employment. It offers a convenient and accessible way for job seekers to explore job opportunities, connect with employers, and manage their job applications.

REFERENCES

Available upon request.